Guide to the Lambda Alpha International, Los Angeles Chapter records, 1981-1985.
Lambda Alpha International, Los Angeles Chapter records, 1981-1985.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lambda Alpha International, Los Angeles Chapter records, 1981-1985.
3594
Lambda Alpha International. Los Angeles Chapter.
2.5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, membership lists, minutes, newsletters, photographs, conference programs, and other papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, membership lists, minutes, Keynotes (newsletter), photographs, conference programs, and other papers.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, membership lists, minutes, Keynotes (newsletter), photographs, conference programs, an intiation ritual from 1982, and other papers.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Lambda Alpha International. Los Angeles Chapter.
Subjects:
Land use--Economic aspects.; Land economics.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Part of Lambda Alpha Literary Archives.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Los Angeles Chapter
  - Meetings, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Initiation ritual, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Member photos - 1983 directory (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Uninitiated member certificates, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Keynotes, 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Keynotes, 1992-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Keynotes, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rosters and dues (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Huston, et al. - Development Agreements Study, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Huston, Flavin, and Haring - Growth Management Study (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Gobar study - Inversion of Traditional Land Value Hierarchies, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Growth Control Study, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Organizational documents (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Organization by-laws, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Misc. publications, 1991-2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Administration: letterhead (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Administration: New member nomination forms (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Awards: Ely Award, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Awards: Other awards (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Awards: Skyline Award, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Speakers Program: Monthly speakers, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Speakers Program: Monthly speakers, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Speakers Program: Monthly speakers, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors: Minutes of meetings, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors: Minutes of meetings, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors: Minutes of meetings, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors: Minutes of meetings, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors: Minutes of meetings, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors: Minutes of meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Skyline Award, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Skyline Award - Paramount Pictures, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Initiation data - City Club on Bunker Hill, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Inactive members, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Skyline Award, 1994, 1996, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Skyline Award, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Initiation Banquet programs, 1978-2002 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - New initiates, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 39A)
  - Annual initiates (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Speakers Program, 1991-2000 (Box 1, Folder 41-42)
  - Meeting notices (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Membership Survey - Survey & results, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Membership Survey - Survey & results, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Board minutes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Board minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Board minutes, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board minutes, 1994-2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board minutes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Japan presentation, May 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Membership list, ca. 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Past presidents (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Summit meetings (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship and mentorship programs (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Student seminar, Nov. 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Skyline Award, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Membership Directory, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Series II. National Organization
  - Keynotes, 1986-1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Keynotes, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - LAISA chapters, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - LAISA - Organization policy statement, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - LAISA membership directory, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - LEF - Organization: Scholarship, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - LEF: Scholarship, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Model manual, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 2001 Awards Committee (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
  - Membership Directory, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Membership Directory, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Membership (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Baltimore study, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Chapter by-laws, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Constitution, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Historian (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Members-at-large, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "Shaping Community: The Choices We Make," Symposium, Chicago, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Cypher dissertation, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Meetings
    - Los Angeles, Oct. 1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Mexico City, Nov. 1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Boston, May 1995 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Vancouver, B.C., Oct. 1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - New Jersey, Apr. 1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - San Diego, Oct. 1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Toronto, May 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Memphis, Oct. 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Phoenix, May 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Charlotte, NC, Nov. 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles, Apr. 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - London, Sept. 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Baltimore, Apr. 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Chicago, Oct. 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    - San Francisco, Apr. 2001 (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
    - Philadelphia, Oct. 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - Vancouver, B.C., May 2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - New York, Oct. 2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)